Prince Singh

Full Stack Web-Developer



Pangalaore , karnataka in Prince Singh 🖈 Portfolio

mrprincesingh

EDUCATION

BCA

Manipal university Jaipur

01/2023 - present | Jaipur, Rajasthan

Full Stack Web development

Masai School

04/2022 – present | Bangalore, Karnataka Full time Course

12th

Narayana Pu College

04/2016 - 04/2018 | Bangalore, Karnataka

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML-5 || CSS-3 || JAVASCRIPT || JSON || REACT || REDUX || CHAKRA-UI || NETLIFY || GITHUB|| MONGO DB|| DATA STRUCTURES AND ALGORITHM

♀ SOFT SKILLS

Leadership Skills, Problem solving Skills ,Communication Skills

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

FSL - First-Source-Pvt-LTD

Customer Care Executive

09/2021 - 03/2022 | Bangalore, India

Worked as a customer care executive Inbond at First Source PVT LTD in a process called Bank of Baroda

BPO Convergence

Customer Care Executive

03/2021 - 09/2021 | Delhi, india

Worked as a customer care executive Inbound at BPO **CONVERGENCE** in a process called SHIPROCKET

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full-Stack Developer with expertise in designing and maintaining websites and systems, writing optimized code and utilizing multiple front-end languages and libraries. With a focus on independent platform functionality, excels in developing digital solutions that meet specific business needs while staying up-to-date with industry trends.

PROIECTS

DERMSTORE CLONE @

Check Live 🔗

Tech Stack :- HTML || CSS || JAVASCRIPT

DermStore is an E-commerce platform offering professional-strength

formulas from top skin care brands A collaborative project built by a team of 5 executed in 4 days

Area of Responsibility

- worked on Navbar
- · worked on Footer
- · Cart Page
- Checkout Page

Features

- Attractive Navbar
- Calculations / Delete Product

Airtable.com - Clone €

Check Live 🔗

Tech Stack :- HTML-5 || CSS-3 || JAVASCRIPT || React.js || Redux || Chakra UI

Airtable is a Task Management tool, People around the world use. Airtable to do everything from cattle tracking to filmmaking. Collaborative project built by a team of 5 and executed in 4 days.

Area of Responsibility

- · Login Page
- resource page
- Single Resource page

Features

- Features
- Login functionality with complete form validation

My Glamm Clone 🔗

Check Live &

Tech Stack: - HTML-5 || CSS-3 || JAVASCRIPT || JSON

My Glamm is an E-commerce platform which is specialized in Beauty

Products. A collaborative project in which I was the team lead. it was built by a team of 5 and executed in 4 days.

Area of Responsibility

- · worked on Navbar
- · worked on Footer
- · Cart Page
- Checkout Page

Features

- Used Heroko, made client page to add data
- Scroll feature for viewing product images